

Marijana Simakoska

Nationality: Macedonian/citizen of the Republic of North Macedonia

**** (+389) 78252791

Date of birth: 27/01/1984

Gender: Female

Email address: marijanatsimakoska@gmail.com

• Address: Bulevar1vi Maj 268, 7000 Bitola (North Macedonia)

ABOUT ME

Passionate, Creative, and Energetic Wedding Planner with eight years of professional experience in the fast-paced Wedding and Event Planning industry. Possess a highly professional attitude, extensive communication/leadership skills, strong attention to detail. Also, Possess ability to operate under deadlines and utilize personal initiative. I have experience with data entry in software systems, data transfer, record updates, excellent knowledge of Word, Excel Spreadsheet program, PowerPoint, and Corel X10.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Administrator for data entry

FAMIS Faculty of Administration and Management Information Systems [01/11/2009 – 01/09/2012]

Address: 1vi Maj 66, Bitola, 7000 Bitola (North Macedonia)

https://www.uklo.edu.mk/

Insurance Manager

FTU Faculty of Tourism and Hospitality [01/09/2002 – 12/01/2009]

Address: Kej Makedonija 75, Ohrid, 6000 Охрид (North Macedonia)

https://ftu.uklo.edu.mk/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Data base administrator

SETTE Clipping [01/01/2020 – Current]

City: Bitola

Country: North Macedonia

- responsible for updating, retrieving, and maintaining information contained in the firm's computers
- involves carrying out tasks such as transferring paper information into computer folders or files
- work with Word Processor and Spreadsheet software to input data, including data that are related to surveys, sales, statistics and client information, to the computer.
- confirmation of customer account information entered and correction, assessment and corrections, as well as re-entry of information when incomplete
- work with external customers and firms

Event and project manager

I Do [10/07/2012 – 31/12/2019]

City: Bitola

Country: North Macedonia

- Design, planning and management of: Party celebrations, Bachelor parties, Wedding ceremonies, Wedding receptions.
- Determining whether it is an outdoor or indoor event Planning events, ranging from 10-500 people.
- Conducting personal and telephone meetings with clients to understand their needs and goals at the event / wedding, the date of the event, the time and place of the events Inspiring customers with ideas for decorations, theme, colors, catering materials and all other details of the event.
- Creating user plans for events that fit the vision and budget of the clients.
- Maintain professional relationships with vendors and venues, such as florists, photographers, caterers (hotels and restaurants), bakers and invitation designers
- Negotiation agreements with selected sellers and making payments as needed
- Arranging the necessary materials for the wedding and equipment for timely transfer to the place / wedding
- Communicate with clients and their families to address last minute needs or changes
- Monitor all activities on the wedding day to make sure everything goes well and in order

Insurance office clerk

AD Croatia Insurance [22/11/2011 – 31/05/2012]

City: Ohrid

Country: North Macedonia

- Responsible for the sale and negotiation of life insurance, health insurance, property or other types of insurance.
- Scheduled daily phone calls and meetings with clients to attract new business activities.
- Responsible for calculating premium amounts and setting payment methods.
- Attend meetings, seminars and programs to learn about new products, policies, services and their pricing.
- Responsible for sales volume analysis, retention and loss and similar services.

DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft Office / Microsoft Excel / Microsoft Word / Zoom / Instagram / Power Point / Data Entry / COREL Corel Draw 10 / Google Suite: Gmail, Google Drive, Google Slide, Google Docs, Google Sheets, Google Forms, Google

COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Posses:

- Awareness (of yourself and others)
- Caring about other people.
- Collaborating and working well together with others.
- Comforting people when they need it.
- Clear communication skills.
- Conflict management and resolution skills.
- Constructive feedback
- Active listening
- Teamwork.
- Responsibility
- Leadership
- Motivation
- Flexibility
- Patience

ORGANISATIONAL SKILLS

Posses:

- Creating and keeping deadlines.
- Goal setting and meeting goals.
- Decision making.
- Managing appointments.
- Team management.
- Project management.
- Making schedules
- Multitasking
- Problem solving

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s):

Macedonian

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B2 READING C1 WRITING C1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Creative works

- Traveling
- Reading books
- Cooking
- Yoga
- Nature walks
- Making creative items from paper and jewelry
- Making creative invitations.

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: B